

Jianming Fan

My address:



Lupinvænget 1 6840 Oksbøl



My mobile number: 26367165



My e- mail address: fanjaney9@gmail.com



WORKING EXPERIENCE

03.2014-02.2016 Online shop

Job responsibility:

- I opened an online shop on Taobao (China's biggest online shopping website) that sold women and children's clothes and accessories.

03.2014-02.2016 Cache Cache-Groupe Beaumanoir, as a Senior merchandiser

Job responsibility:

- Participated in expanding and launching new webistes e-commerce shops.
- Assigned and coordinated orders production.
- Collaborated well with designers, supplies and customer services department.
- Organzied new product launches each season.

12.2010-06.2013 The Children's Place, as a Senior merchandiser

Job responsibility:

- Assigned orders and coordinated bulk production.
- Established and maintained a strong supplier network.
- Collaborated with designers and arranged photo shooting.
- Organzied sales meeting and negotiated prices with vendors.
- Arranged tests for garments and accessories.

08.2002-11.2010 Novelle Joie Limited as a Merchandiser

Job responsibility:

- Collaborated with designers.
- Made arrangements of sample and customer meetings.
- Developed excellent customer service skills.
- Prepared samples approval and tests, including coordination of deliveries, shipping methods and customs clearance.



SKILLS ·····

IT skills: Graphic Design, Video Production, Adobe Creative Suite, Website content creation, Photography, Powerpoint, Javascript, Wordpress, Html, CSS.

Language skills: Can speak chinese, english and danish fluently. **Licenses:** Driving license.



EDUCATION BACKGROUND ·

08.2021-present Erhvervs akademi sydvest

Major: Multimedia design

Courses: Web design and development, content creation, content management system, video production, user experience.

09.1999-07.2002 Shanghai University of Technology

Major: Mechatronics Technology (AP degree)

Courses: Engineering CAD & Drafting, Electrical Systems, Me-

chanical Systems.



02.2017-06. 2019 Language school in Varde

Prøve i Dansk 2: 12.

08.2019-06.2021 VUC in Esbjerg (9/10. class)

Danish D: 12



PERSONAL STATEMENT

I come from China, I moved to Danmark with my family 5 years ago and I have around 14 years of working experience in the field of international trade and e-commerce. I have worked as a senior merchandiser for two famous international clothes companies, the Children's Place and Cache-Cache Groupe Beaumanoir for many years, so I have extensive experience in retail, marketing and e-commerce platforms.

I am good at corrdination and cooperation. I have strong anlytical and problem solving skills. I am optimistic, positive, responsible and can work under stress. I can provide strong support to my boss and colleagues. I can write and speak Chinese, English and Danish fluently. I am passionate about keeping up to date with the latest technologies coming on to the market and am dedicated to working in the multimedia designer industry.